Guide to the Records of the Women's Philharmonic M1470
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series XIV: Guest Artists
  - !0/21/89 Geraldine Walther (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Nan Washburn 11/21/91, 11/23/91 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - October 8 1994, Roxanne Weinberger viola (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - March 3 and 4 1990; Liu Weishan (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Wolfensohn, Sara -- piano (Box 63, Folder 26)
  - January 28 1995 Sarah Wolfensen piano (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Zhang, Yan (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Joann Polk (pianist), Amy Beach (composer) 1999 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Portillo, Lourdes (video/film) (Box 64, Folder 21)
  - Fujimoto, Akiko 1997 (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Denisch, Beth (Box 54, Folder 41)
  - Min Xiao-Fen March 1, 1997: appearance contract/materials (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Tobias, Paul (cellist) (Box 62, Folder 31)
  - Artist Information Exchange Submission Form/Mailing Labels (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Series XV: Production Materials
  Production Materials
  This contains information concerning venue logistics, program production notes, artist materials and correspondence relating to the planning of each season and concert of the Women's Philharmonic. Also contains materials, notes and correspondence about the Women's Philharmonic annual Galas, the Eleanor Roosevelt concert, vendor donations, venue logistics and salon events.
  - Video premier Sept. 1992 (Box 108, Folder 7)
  - 1983-84 Season program planning (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - 1988-89 Season (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - 1988-89 Production Notes (Box 42, Folder 36)
  - 1988-89 Children's Concerts (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Legion of Honor Concert 1988-89 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Legion of Honor Concerts 1988-89 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Children's Concert Feb.22-23, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - 11/2 & 3 1989 Children's Concerts (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - 1989-1990 Season (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - 1989-1990 Season: miscellaneous correspondence and documents; mock-ups of concert brochures (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Feb 11, 1989 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - March 11 1989 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - March 11, 1989 Ursula Lequin (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - April 20, 1989 concert material (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - October 21 1989 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - 10/21/1989 Geraldine Walther (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - October 1989 Concert (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - 1990-1991 Season (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - 1990-1991 Season Programming (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Tenth Anniversary Season 1990-91 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - 2/3/1990 Oakland Symphony Chorus (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - February 3, 1990 Oakland Symphony Chorus (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - 3/3/1990 Pacific Rim (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - 4/20/90 Susan Slaughter (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - 10/6/1990 Paula Robison (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - 11/2&3/1990 New American Music (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - 11/3/1990 New American Music (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - 1991-92 Season (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - 1991-92 Season (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - 1/23/1991 Nan Washburn/Jennifer Paul (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - 2/9/91 Comet-La Barbara (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - 2/6/1991 Comet / La Barbara (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - 3/21&23/1991 Deborah Schwartz (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - 4/27/1991 Soviet Composers concert notes (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - 1992-93 season (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - 1992-1993 Season materials (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Kennedy Center 1/12/92 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Oberlin Dance Collective (ODC) 2/1/1992 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - 1992-1993 Concert program printing (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - 1992 Stern Grove/Villa Montalvo venue logisitics (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - Villa Montalvo/Stern Grove performance notes 1992 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - October 3, 1992 concert program materials (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - October 3, 1992, Eugenia Zuckerman, flute: concert materials (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - 10/3/1992 Eugenia Zuckerman (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - November 14, 1992: Heather Buchman, trombone (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - November 14, 1992 Concert program materials (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - 1993-1994 Season notes (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - 1993-1994 Season Materials (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - February 6, 1993: Krista Smith, Horn (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Feb 6 1993 Concert (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - 2/6/1993 Krista Smith (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Children's Concerts; 3/1993 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - March 5 & 6, 1993: Bobby McFerrin/Oberlin Dance Collective (ODC) (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - 4/13/1993 Concert Program (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - May 8 1993; Concert and Program Booklet (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - October 2, 1993 Israeli/Jewish Program Materials (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - October 2, 1993 Program book materials (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - 11/20/1993 Concert notes (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - November 21, 1993 concert program (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Nov. 20 1993 Concert materials (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - 1994-95 Season (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - 1994-95 season (letters/memos) (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - January 29, 1994 Production (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - January 29, 1994 Program book materials (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - February 1994 concert materials (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - February 25 & 26 1994 Latina Program booklet materials (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - February 25 & 26, 1994: Latina Program materials (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - May 21 & 22, 1994 Eastern European program materials (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Lindsay Cooper (guest bassoonist) Visa/Immigration Materials 1994 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - May 21, 1994 Concert program booklet materials (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - May 21, 1994 Eastern European Concert materials (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - October 8, 1994 program booklet (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - November 21, 1994 Northern European Program Materials (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - 1995-96 Season notes (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - 1995-1996 Season (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - January 28, 1995 program booklet (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - March 11, 1995 Chamber (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - March 11, 1995 program booklet (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - May 6, 1995 program booklet (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - May 23, 1995 Benefit Concert WP Chamber Players (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - 8/12/1995 Concert (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Myths and Poems of China Chen Yi 4/24/1996 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Chamber Ensemble Gig 9/1996 (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - 1997/98 Season Brochure (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Salon 1997-1998 Production/logistic Notes (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - 1/25/1997 15th Anniversary (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - 2/7/98 World Premier of Ekizian Piano Concerto (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - 4/15/1997 Women's Philharmonic 16th Season (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Concert Information 1998-99 Season (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - 5/1/98 1998-99 Season Programs (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - 2/7/98 World Premier Piano Concerto (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Photos correspondence re: Thea Musgrave and 01/23/1998 Concert (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - 3/7/98 WP Brass Quintet and Karen Clark Presents Works by Women Composers (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - 7/1/98 Music in the Making (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - November 14 1998 Concert program materials (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - November 14, 1998 Concert production notes (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - November 14, 1998 program booklet materials (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - December 10, 1998 Program booklet materials (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - 1998/1999 season program notes (Box 84, Folder 13)
  - 1998/1999 Season planning notes (Box 84, Folder 12)
  - 1998/1999 Herbst Theater information (Box 84, Folder 11)
  - 1999-2000 Season (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - 1999-2000 Season notes (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - 1999-2000 Season Planning (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Season Planning 1999/2000 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - 1999-2000 Yerba Buena Center for the Arts (YBCA) (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - January 23, 1999 Concert program materials (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - January 23, 1999 Concert production (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - 4/2/1999 New Season 1999-2000 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - April 3 1999 Concert program materials (Box 84, Folder 10)
  - April 3, 1999 Concert production (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - Salon, April 3, 1999 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - May 28, 1999 Concert Program materials (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - May 28, 1999 Concert production (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - May 28, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - May 28 Concert 5/28/1999 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Event Entertainment 1999 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Opening Night Gala October 16, 1999 (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - Confirmed Food Donations for Gala: October 16, 1999 (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - Gala October 16, 1999 Invitations (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - 10/16/1999 Production (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - 10/16/1999 Program notes (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Restaurants Confirmed for October 16, 1999 (Box 71, Folder 15)
  - Declined Food Donations 1999 (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - Vorpal Gallery Rental fee/specs 1999 (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - Gala Concert Dinner Correspondence/Planning 1999 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - 2000 Season (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - 2000-2001 Season Planning (Box 71, Folder 25)
  - 2000-2001 Season notes (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - 02/26/2000 Production notes (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - 02/26/2000 Program notes (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - 2/26/00 Concert Production/Program (Box 67, Folder 22)
  - 03/25/2000 Program notes (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - 03/25/2000 Production notes (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - 3/25/00 Concert Production/Program (Box 67, Folder 21)
  - March 25, 2000 Production (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - 25 March 2000 Concert Materials (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - April 15, 2000; Special concert (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - April 15, 2000; Charlotte Church (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Women's Philharmonic/Charlotte Church 04/15/2000 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - 05/26/2000 Program and Misc. Materials (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - September 30, 2000 set 1 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Nov. 24, 2000 Program Book Info (Box 64, Folder 20)
  - Rudolph Cleare 11/24/2000 Program Notes: Negro Spirituals (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - Nov. 24, 2000 Concert (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - 2001/02 Season Planning (Box 63, Folder 19)
  - 2001 Performances with other groups (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - March 10, 2001 Concert (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - 5/13/2001 Luther, Wagner, Larsen, Boulanger concert notes (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - May 13, 2001 Concert (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Papillon IV Concert series 2004 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Middle School Program: Chen Yi (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - International Women's Day Programming (Box 64, Folder 25)
  - Annual Gala production
    Annual Gala
    This series contains all notes and materials pertaining to the planning and production of the Women's Philharmonic annual gala concert and after parties.
    - Gala PR (Box 42, Folder 20)
    - Gala 1992-93 (Box 42, Folder 23)
    - A Concert Honoring Eleanor Roosevelt (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - 20th Anniversary Season (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - 2001-02 Season 20th Anniv (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - 10/3/92 Opening Night Gala (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - Reception Gala 2000 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Gala 10-8-1994 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - 2000/01 Opening Night Gala (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Opening Night Gala Vorpal Gallery 10/16/99 (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Gala concert 2000 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - 2000-2001 Gala notes (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - 1999 Opening night gala + post-concert parties materials (Box 95, Folder 9)
    - 20th Anniversary Season 2001 - 2002 materials (Box 104, Folder 9)
    - 2001 - 2002 Gala for 20th Anniversary (Box 104, Folder 10)
    - Gala materials 1992-1993 (Box 108, Folder 9)
    - Gala October 2, 1993-1994 (Box 108, Folder 10)
    - Gala 1986-1987 materials (Box 108, Folder 11)
    - 1999-2000 Opening Night Gala (Box 119, Folder 8)
    - Opening Night 2000-2001 (Box 121, Folder 12)
    - Opening Night Nov. 14, 1998 (Box 121, Folder 13)
  - April 3 concert materials (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - February 26, 2000 concert materials (Box 95, Folder 10)
  - Concert/Reception (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Feb 6 Concert (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - February Concert (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - January Legion of Honor (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Legion of Honor (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Making Waves (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - May Concert (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Nov. 24th Concert (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Kennedy Center Program Notes 1991 (Box 88, Folder 15)
  - Feb. 1, 1992 Concert production materials (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - 1992-1993 Season notes (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - Program notes 1993-1994 (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - Nov. 14, 1992 program notes (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - Oct. 3, 1992 concert notes (Box 89, Folder 9)
  - 1992 Repertoire recommendations (Box 89, Folder 11)
  - Zeum: rental fees + specs. (Box 64, Folder 22)
  - 1997 Misc. Promotional Materials (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - May 2, 1998 concert materials (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Artistic Planning 2001-02 (Box 57, Folder 20)
  - 2/1/1992 Oberlin Dance Coll. (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - 2/1/1992 Oberlin Dance Coll. (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - March 8, 2001 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - March 1, 1997 Program booklet/materials (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - March 1, 1997: J. Karla Lemon production notes (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - March 27, 1997 Concert complimentary tickets (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - March 1, 1997 concert complimentary tickets (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - Jan. 25, 1997 production folder (Box 93, Folder 8)
  - 1996-1997 Program booklet: Jan. 25, 1997 (Box 93, Folder 10)
  - 1996-1997 Season Concert complimentary tickets (Box 93, Folder 11)
  - 1996-1997 Season notes (Box 93, Folder 12)
  - 1996-1997 Season brochure (Box 93, Folder 13)
  - Animating Democracy (Box 64, Folder 17)
  - Postponed 1994-95 Program Plans (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - 2001-2002 season draft (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - 1999-2000 Season materials (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - September 30, 2000 Hsu/Kotova concert materials (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - November 24, 2000 Hsu/Tillery/CHC concert notes (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - May 13, 2001 Hsu/Boyd concert notes (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - Season materials, 2001-2002 (Box 148, Folder 11)
  - 1999-2000 season budget materials (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - March 25, 2000 Post-concert event materials (Box 95, Folder 12)
  - May 26, 2000 Cancer resource Center concert materials (Box 95, Folder 13)
  - Concert May 26, 2000: Joint USF Cancer Res. Ctr. materials (Box 95, Folder 14)
  - June 1996 Festival program materials (Box 95, Folder 16)
  - Woodwind quintet notes (Box 95, Folder 17)
  - 2001-2002 Season planning notes + correspondence (Box 95, Folder 18)
  - Roosevelt Concert
    Eleanor Roosevelt Concert
    This includes all materials pertaining to the development and production of the 1998 Eleanor Roosevelt concert.
    - 12/10/98 (Roosevelt) Press Release (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - 10/9/98 Roosevelt Press Release (Box 25, Folder 32)
    - 11/20/98 Roosevelt Concert Press Release (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - SF Chronicle: Hsu's baton to honor Roosevelt (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - SJ Mercury News: 12/12/1998 Homage to rebel Eleanor Roosevelt (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Roosevelt Letters (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Eleanor Roosevelt Concert: donors (Box 88, Folder 11)
    - Eleanor Roosevelt Project (Box 88, Folder 12)
    - Eleanor Roosevelt concert materials (Box 88, Folder 13)
    - Working Assets Presents: A concert tribute to Eleanor Roosevelt, Dec. 10, 1998 (Box 94, Folder 7)
    - Eleanor Roosevelt Concert: Offenhartz dinner (1998) (Box 94, Folder 8)
    - Eleanor Roosevelt production materials (Box 94, Folder 9)
    - Eleanor Roosevelt: fundraising notes (Box 94, Folder 10)
    - Eleanor Roosevelt concert honorary committee (Box 94, Folder 11)
    - Working Assets and E. Roosevelt marketing materials (Box 117, Folder 15)
    - Eleanor Roosevelt / Working assests sponsorship, 12/10/1998 (Box 150, Folder 15)
    - Eleanor Roosevelt materials (Box 151, Folder 3)
  - Music Education concerts/development
    Music education
    This sub-series contains information, notes, planning materials regarding the Women's Philharmonic involvement with music education and local schools.
    - Education-music Women's Phil. kids concerts materials (Box 95, Folder 15)
    - Children's Concert (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - 1997-1998 Educational program ideas: other orchestras (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - Arts programs for schools materials: 2000-2001 (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - Women's Phil: "Youth Movements" 1991 materials (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - "A Leap Across the Barlines" (1992) educational video by the Women's Phil. (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - Educational video notes (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - Children's video notes + materials (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - "A Leap Across the Barlines" award notices (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - 1992 Women's Phil. Children's concerts notes + materials (Box 97, Folder 8)
    - 1993 Children's concerts materials (Box 97, Folder 9)
    - "Music Magic" video series materials (Box 97, Folder 10)
    - 1993 Education materials (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - 1993 music education materials (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - New Women Composer Resource Center + Music Ed. materials (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - 1992 Musid ed. resources (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - 1992 Misc. music ed. resources (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - Young Audiences (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Montclair Women's Cultural Arts Club (venue info) (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - 1984-85 Season (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Mexican Museum (Box 64, Folder 34)
  - March 8, 2001 Spaulding gig materials (Box 104, Folder 7)
  - The Women's Building May 2001 concert (Box 104, Folder 8)
  - Staff/Production meeting notes 2000 - 2001 (Box 104, Folder 11)
  - Wednesday March 28 2001 meeting notes (Box 104, Folder 12)
  - Event venues 1996 (Box 107, Folder 11)
  - Assorted invitation samples (other organizations) (Box 107, Folder 12)
  - 1996 event calendar (Box 107, Folder 19)
  - Special events (catering, venues and donors) (Box 107, Folder 24)
  - Art space-SF (Box 62, Folder 23)
  - Program Notes 11/15/97 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Program Notes (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - 1st Congregational Church Renovation (venue notes) (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Concert Halls (part I) (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Concert Halls (part II) (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Misc. Venues: rental prices + logistics (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Venue notes (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Venues/Reherasal Locations (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Yerba Buena Copy Input (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Dee Braig Project (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - 1994-95 Season General information (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - May 1992 Dress rehearsal reception materials (Box 108, Folder 8)
  - July 23, 1995 Welcome party for Executive Director Judy Patrick materials (Box 108, Folder 15)
  - November 1997 Musicians thank you event (Box 108, Folder 19)
  - Social/Fundraising events
    Fundraising events
    This includes materials, notes and correspondences regarding the production and planning of various fundaraising events that the Women's Philharmonic hosted. These dinners, tea parties, auctions or other social events enabled donors and potential donors or subscribers to meet conductors, composers or guest artists.
    - Joint fundraising with Chanticleer for June 1996 concerts (Box 107, Folder 20)
    - Bramhall event (major donor cultivation) May 5, 1995 (Box 107, Folder 17)
    - Special events check list (Box 107, Folder 14)
    - Women's Phil. Event planning form (Box 107, Folder 13)
    - 1995-1996 House parties (Box 107, Folder 15)
    - Misc. event discussion notes 1995 (Box 107, Folder 16)
    - Joann Falletta event June 16, 1996 (Box 107, Folder 18)
    - Shirley Hort event January 24, 1998 (donor brunch) (Box 107, Folder 23)
    - Major Donor dinner October 1997 (Box 107, Folder 22)
    - June 1991 Country Western dance fundraiser (Box 108, Folder 6)
    - Babe's at Betty's Diner event May 1991 (Box 108, Folder 13)
    - Russian Tea Party reception April 27 1991 (Box 108, Folder 12)
    - Sept. 9, 1992 Country Western Dance fundraiser (Box 108, Folder 14)
    - Meet the Composer event June 14, 1996 (Box 108, Folder 16)
    - Melissa Smith tea May 4 1996 (Box 108, Folder 17)
    - April 20, 1996 Judy Bloom dinner event (Box 108, Folder 18)
    - Victoria Bond/ Kay Taylor party and reception 1993 (Box 109, Folder 1)
    - Tsippi Fleisher reception Sept. 1993 (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - composer in residence reception: Chen Yi; Sept. 1993 (Box 109, Folder 3)
    - May 18, 1996: Spaulding cultivation event (Box 109, Folder 4)
    - May 1993 Donor dinner (Box 109, Folder 5)
    - Volunteer list: March 29 1997 reception (Box 109, Folder 7)
    - Miriam Abrams tribute dinner May 1993 (Box 109, Folder 8)
    - Musician's reception March 31, 1993 (Box 109, Folder 12)
    - Special Events (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Silent auction planning materials 1996 (Box 118, Folder 8)
    - Scharffenberger Silent auction 1996 (Box 118, Folder 9)
    - Scharffenberger press and program materials (Box 118, Folder 10)
    - Donor cocktail event March 16 1997 (Box 118, Folder 11)
    - Scharffenberger general and misc. information (Box 118, Folder 12)
    - Scharffenberger event notes (Box 118, Folder 13)
    - Scharffenberger invoices, budget and reconciliation materials (Box 118, Folder 14)
    - Scharffenberger Invitations list and materials (Box 118, Folder 15)
    - Judy Patrick 50th birthday party (Box 118, Folder 16)
    - October 1998 Event auction (Box 118, Folder 17)
    - October 1998 event: budgets and actuals (Box 118, Folder 18)
    - UCSF Cancer Resource Center May 26, 2000 benefit (Box 119, Folder 1)
    - Major Donor event Fall 1999 (Box 119, Folder 2)
    - Misc. Event materials 1995 (Box 119, Folder 5)
    - Honorary Committtee materials for OCt. 3 1998 event (Box 119, Folder 6)
    - "A Few Good Women" event materials October 3, 1998 (Box 119, Folder 7)
    - Azzani breakfast October 25, 2000 (Box 119, Folder 9)
    - Tea party background (Box 151, Folder 1)
    - Wine (Box 151, Folder 2)
    - Lenya Bernstein Barnes / Judy Patrick 50th gala (Box 151, Folder 6)
  - May 2, 1998 concert production (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - March 7, 1998 concert production (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - February 7 1998 concert production (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Feb 7, 1998 comp tickets list (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - March 7, 1998 program booklet (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - February 7, 1998 program book (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - Nov. 15, 1997 program book (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - June 8, 19979 New Music Reading Session production notes (Box 116, Folder 8)
  - Nov. 15, 1997 comp tickets list (Box 116, Folder 9)
  - 1997-1998 season ticket comps (Box 116, Folder 10)
  - Nov. 15, 1997 concert production (Box 116, Folder 11)
  - 1997-1998 Herbst Theatre logistics (Box 116, Folder 12)
  - 1997-1998 season planning (Box 116, Folder 13)
  - May 2, 1998 Program book (Box 116, Folder 14)
  - March 1991 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - November 1990 Sacramento (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - February 1991 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - October 1990 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Final 02/2005 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Community Music Center (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - 2002 production notes (Box 32, Folder 30)
  - Bay Area Women's Phil Wine donation letters 1988-1992 (Box 109, Folder 11)
  - Old wine donation contacts (1990s) (Box 108, Folder 5)
  - Food donations 1995-1996 (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - Wine donations (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - Hotels/Printing/Air travel: donations 1994-1996 (Box 108, Folder 2)
  - Wu Han March 25, 1997 Concert appearance materials (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - March 29, 1997 concert program materials (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - March 29, 1997 Apo Hsu: concert materials and correspondence (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - June 1996 Chen Yi concert materials (Box 117, Folder 4)
  - June 1996 Chen Yi project and budget materials (Box 117, Folder 5)
  - 1996-1997 season: working budget materials (Box 117, Folder 6)
  - 1999-2000 Season planning (Box 117, Folder 10)
  - March 3, 2002 Stanford Int'l Women's Days concert planning (Box 117, Folder 11)
  - 1998-1999 Concert production; timeline and responsibilities (Box 117, Folder 17)
  - Lighting design; Feb. 27, 1987 concert (Box 117, Folder 18)
  - May 26, 2000: concert production materials (Box 117, Folder 19)
  - Sept. 30 2000 concert production materials (Box 117, Folder 21)
  - 2001-2002 Season: 20th Anniversary notes (Box 117, Folder 22)
  - Event venues and planning notes 2002 (Box 117, Folder 23)
  - 2003 Benefit for the Women's Phil. materials (Box 121, Folder 7)
  - Heroes for the Planet Concert
    Heroes for the Planet